lawctopus.com 2012-12-30

# Lawctopus Policies » Lawctopus

## Policies

We are committed to protect all personally identifiable information and strive for protecting privacy of our users. Please read this document carefully. Suggestions to change/edit/modify these rules are always welcome.

**What information do we collect?** We collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or phone number.

We may also collect information about your computer, your IP address and your use of this website.

**What do we use your information for?** Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:• To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

**How do we protect your information?** We take reasonable care to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. Although we cannot guarantee that any of these measures are foolproof. Please do not submit any information which you would want to keep confidential. **Do we use cookies?**

We do not use cookies.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.

We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links** Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our website’s privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or send an email notifying you of any changes.

This policy was last modified on October 2, 2010.

**Governing Law and Jurisdiction**

****These terms shall be governed by and interpreted in accordance with the laws of India and especially the Information Technology Act, 2000. All relevant rules, regulations, directions, orders and notifications will also apply. The Courts in Kolkata  shall have exclusive jurisdiction to the exclusion of other courts.
